you are channel
press the i found
to see outdated
now in chat
the donor is a
role in a product
that meant team
scrum team
who was response
though for the product
cloud make
ensure that it is
to date and term
the of priorities
and has the
items which tree
the laid back to the
vision
the product owner
represents that this
this or user
and as accountable
for collaborating
the customer
define what features
will be in the prime
released
so what do proud
the owners do
the
all of a product
the owner is really
critical as it
shakes hands at both
fans that
that team and
the stakeholders
the point
the owner works
with the stakeholders
the get the right where
fireman's right
in the sense to
the users device
is the requirement
which they may not
see or com
and at that point
this
the only improves
the relationship with
customers
also helps too
build up the track
the and
the other end
product owner help
the delivery team
or development
team to under
stand the vision
and that required
it's
this role as
kind of bridge
when the two ends
holding tight
the two corners
and effectively and
than the smooth
communication
nan
let us see the differ
the responsibility
the switch a product or
it has to undertake
the vision
the to owner has
responsibility
of creating a vision
so that the does
that meant team
the early visualize
there's the expected
come by the use
it is
the product owner
the major early into
racks and collapse
it's with the users
to understand
their requirements
thus it is
really important
translate that
in a form of
vision to the
him
so it is
cool a significant
to communicate
there's and and goals
to the stakeholders
so that every
one talks the same
language and
the an identical
they're standing of the
come to
make sure every hour
i'm from the goal is
lying to the best
this objectives
the product own
there should create a
the road map
which is a high
the tactical
graphical some
murray that shape
the vision and
action for the
that
managing
product backlog
the most
the essential worse
it's ability in the
the manager
this is managing
the product back
today
the market is really
dynamic
the items in the
product backlog
require some
mintz do to change
jean priorities
it's
product owners
responsibility
build a staff
the items in the back
clark and
your tires them
as per the best
scholes
the product
backlog is a day
then that list of i
what should be free
lee updated
based on changing
project requirement
the all the way through the
that meant
prioritize
the needs
the product
winner has to pray
a ties the proud
the backlog item
in a away
that they deliver
the maximum
come
we live in a world where
help as readily
available and term
that's awesome tools
hence their
the heaps of tools
help product owner
the do this
the product
owner is required
to have the back
sequenced
prior to the sprint
planning meeting
this means
each user's
worry must be
after by relative
the importance
ver si defense
that means stages
once
the have the basic and
tsm place
vision called
the backlog and
the prioritization
the problem
the owner has to make
sure that he or she
is participating
in the overall the
that meant stages
the product
nan
their product owner
to get clarity
the feel queries
my mind as
nan
the item
the product
there will participate
in the ceremonies
with the team in
some ceremonies
this role can be
active such as
planning or back
lol grooming
the can be passive
the or inactive
such as in the daily
graham
evaluate
product private
this at each it
nation
the product
make sure that
development work
upon the priority
these and mana
there's the progress
the items over
the course of a sprint
what
that is either
complete or
i'm done
needs to be real
the or ties or
sequenced
the product
make sure that the
they'll allotment delivers
the expected out
comes from the story
they worked upon
the accepts it
so these
some of the many
responsibilities
scrum product
they're takes
we hope this video
helped you understand
the who a scrum
the donor is
don't forget to
described to our channel
for more videos
and visit our
site for all the
scrum related
sources