my grandma
the over was the
the so
we dust
elderly person
you could it
ever meet
she was
the getting
advanced in
years when she passed
the way a couple of years
ago but she's
not left that
hold her back
she
kept doing her
favorite hobbies
baking cookies
these for the kids
all the time
she likes making
fruit roll ups
so she would
boil up
and strawberries
all kinds of fruit
and dry it
roll it up
and she had these delays
this fruit roll ups
all her grandkids
that's when they came by
so the cookie
was always filled
and there was all
these these delicious
the fruit snacks
the
she will
is just
the beautiful
lady see
the even though she was
vance ten year
there's you know
for a while she was
dying her hair
it black
but then
let it go away
it's an eye
so we adore
how sweet she
with her white
their like
herself
look like
she was getting old
there
no she was
spring chicken
she was eighteen
nine when she passed
the way
and even though she was getting
on in years
still played games
the with us kids
the time we would play
card games
word games
ems
remember when i
the little
lots of times the other
we're adults didn't
play with us
the ads and
they would want to play
the games that the adult
table button
my grandma
could always be
counted on
two
in with the kids
play a game sheet
hot me
play a lot of games
pea knuckle
my parents weren't
patient and after to
sweet pea knuckle bitch
the did she was willing
to teach me that game
she also lived
quilting
often there would be
quilt set up in
the living room that she
the working on with
a thimble
her finger
she does
was the most
kind soul
she was very far
fall oh
is remembering
present on your
birthday
that christmas
she loved throwing
hardy's
and making sure that
people realize
she loved them
the thing and a nice
the things she would do for them
okay that's
few minutes