hear the word
man it is
you think
lamia the
humanity's sound
academic
that really it's all
that exploring what
the make and
the
humanity's deep and
understanding of
we are
and help us make me
and be
the out of our lives
for it
both
say you're in a book club
discussing virginia
well
how about classic
poetry
are you upset
with movie review
for a three by
the series on free
carlo
for a deep
the into world war two
nan
poetry litter
sure history
criticism
they're all part of the human
these
this
that
damn
exploring the arts
then you probably have
if the humanities
nan
maybe you're learning job
the nice for your next thing
haitian
are studying for
the for your fiance
well
language
this era yep
part of the humanity
the
here's the thing
everywhere
the humans
find the humanity
it's about
understanding who we
and the
for me
the together